{"Answer": "Response to a Monovalent 2009 Influenza A (H1N1) Vaccine\n\nA novel 2009 influenza A ( H1N1 ) virus is responsible for the first influenza pandemic in 41 years . A safe and effective vaccine is needed . A randomized , observer-blind , parallel-group trial evaluating two doses of an inactivated , split-virus 2009 H1N1 vaccine in healthy adults between the ages of 18 and 64 years is ongoing at a single site in Australia .\n\nWe evaluated the immunogenicity and safety of the vaccine after each of two scheduled doses , administered 21 days apart . A total of 240 subjects , equally divided into two age groups ( ( 50 years and \u2265 50 years ) , were enrolled and underwent randomization to receive either 15 \u03bcg or 30 \u03bcg of hemagglutinin antigen by intramuscular injection . We measured antibody titers using hemagglutination-inhibition and microneutralization assays at baseline and 21 days after vaccination . The coprimary immunogenicity end points were the proportion of subjects with antibody titers of 1:40 or more on hemagglutination-inhibition assay , the proportion of subjects with either seroconversion or a significant increase in antibody titer , and the factor increase in the geometric mean titer .\n\nBy day 21 after the first dose , antibody titers of 1:40 or more were observed in 114 of 120 subjects ( 95.0 % ) who received the 15-\u03bcg dose and in 106 of 119 subjects ( 89.1 % ) who received the 30-\u03bcg dose . A similar result was observed after the second dose of vaccine . No deaths , serious adverse events , or adverse events of special interest were reported . Local discomfort ( e.g. , injection-site tenderness or pain ) was reported by 56.3 % of subjects , and systemic symptoms ( e.g. , headache ) by 53.8 % of subjects after each dose . Nearly all events were mild to moderate in intensity .\n\nA single 15-\u03bcg dose of 2009 H1N1 vaccine was immunogenic in adults , with mild-to-moderate vaccine-associated reactions . ( ClinicalTrials . gov number ,  NCT00938639  . )\n\n", "Topic": "immunization", "Question": "NEJMoa0907413", "level": 0, "branch": "NEJMoa0907413", "Tagging": {"Coarse": {"hemagglutinin antigen by intramuscular injection": ["Intervention"], "immunogenicity": ["Outcomes"], "15 \u03bcg": ["Intervention"], "30 \u03bcg": ["Intervention"], "240": ["Participants"], "healthy": ["Participants"], "adult": ["Participants"], "18 and 64": ["Participants"], "21": ["Intervention"], "114 of 120": ["Outcomes"], "95.0 %": ["Outcomes"], "106 of 119": ["Outcomes"], "89.1 %": ["Outcomes"], "local discomfort": ["Outcomes"], "systemic symptom": ["Outcomes"], "australia": ["Participants"], "2009 h1n1 vaccine": ["Intervention"]}, "Fine": {"immunogenicity": ["Outcomes-general"], "15 \u03bcg": ["Intensity"], "30 \u03bcg": ["Intensity"], "240": ["Sample-size"], "healthy": ["Condition"], "adult": ["Age"], "18 and 64": ["Age"], "21": ["Duration"], "114 of 120": ["Effect-strength"], "95.0 %": ["Effect-strength"], "106 of 119": ["Effect-strength"], "89.1 %": ["Effect-strength"], "local discomfort": ["Adverse-effects"], "systemic symptom": ["Adverse-effects"], "australia": ["Location"], "2009 h1n1 vaccine": ["Intervention-general"]}}, "Doggos_crowd": {"Coarse": {"Participants": ["A", "A", "A", "A"], "Intervention": ["A", "A", "A"], "Outcomes": ["A", "A", "A"], "Conclusion": ["A"]}, "Fine": {"Sex": [], "Age": ["A"], "Condition": ["A"], "Location": ["A"], "Sample-size": ["A"], "Intervention-general": ["A"], "Duration": ["A"], "Intensity": ["A"], "Control": [], "Outcomes-general": ["A"], "Effect-strength": ["A"], "Adverse-effects": ["A"], "Conclusion-general": ["A"]}, "Count": 1}, "Doggos_text": {"Age": "The study was performed on adults between the ages of 18 and 64.", "Condition": "The study was performed in healthy participants.", "Location": "The study was performed at a single site in Australia.", "Sample-size": "There were a total of 240 participants.", "Intervention-general": "The study assessed the 2009 H1N1 vaccine.", "Duration": "Effects were assessed 21 days after.", "Intensity": "Subjects were randomized to receive two dosages of vaccines with either 15 \u03bcg or 30 \u03bcg of hemagglutinin antigen by intramuscular injection.", "Outcomes-general": "The study measured the immunogenicity H1N1 vaccine.", "Effect-strength": "Antibody titers of 1:40 or more were observed in 114 of 120 (or 95%) of the subjects who received the 15 \u03bcg dose and in 106 of 119  (or 89%)  of the subject who received the 30 \u03bcg dose.", "Adverse-effects": "Local discomfort was reported by 56.3% of the subjects and systemic symptoms by 53.8% after each dose.", "Conclusion-general": "A single 15 \u03bcg dose of 2009 H1N1 vaccine was immunogenic in adults, with mild-to-moderate vaccine associated reactions."}, "id": "NEJMoa0907413", "children": [{"Answer": "A 2009 influenza A (H1N1) virus is the cause for the first influenza pandemic since 41 years. Adults between 18 and 64 years old are receiving two doses of an inactivated, split-virus 2009 H1N1 vaccine for a group trail in Australia. There is a total of 240 people equally divided by age, each person receiving 2 vaccines 21 days apart. People randomly chosen either got a 15 ug or 30 ug dose. Antibody titers were measured using hemagglutination-inhibition and microneutralization assays before and 21 days after vaccination was received. The end points for coprimary immunogenicity were those who had antibody titers of 1:40 or more on hemagglutination-inhibition assay.&#13;&#13;21 days after the first does, 114 of 120 people that received 15-ug had titers 1:40 or more (95%). Out of 119 people who received 30-ug dosage only 106 had titers of 1:40 or more. (89.1%). After the second dose the result was similar. No one seemed to have been affected by the vaccine.  Discomfort at the injection site was reported by 56.3% of the people. 53.8% reported symptoms like headaches. ", "AssignmentId": "3R8YZBNQ9I37ZWCZDS5NHASYBGYQ7U", "Question": "NEJMoa0907413", "WorkerId": "A3RZLDKSVK9W3N", "Qualification": 0.875, "Topic": "immunization", "Hop": 0, "Education": "Some College", "Gender": "female", "Age": "24-39", "level": 1, "branch": "NEJMoa0907413", "Tagging": {"Coarse": {"immunogenicity": ["Outcomes"], "240": ["Participants"], "adult": ["Participants"], "18 and 64": ["Participants"], "21": ["Intervention"], "114 of 120": ["Outcomes"], "89.1 %": ["Outcomes"], "australia": ["Participants"], "2009 h1n1 vaccine": ["Intervention"]}, "Fine": {"immunogenicity": ["Outcomes-general"], "240": ["Sample-size"], "adult": ["Age"], "18 and 64": ["Age"], "21": ["Duration"], "114 of 120": ["Effect-strength"], "89.1 %": ["Effect-strength"], "australia": ["Location"], "2009 h1n1 vaccine": ["Intervention-general"]}}, "Doggos_crowd": {"Coarse": {"Participants": ["A", "C", "B", "A"], "Intervention": ["A", "A", "A"], "Outcomes": ["A", "A", "A"], "Conclusion": ["D"]}, "Fine": {"Age": ["A"], "Condition": ["C"], "Location": ["B"], "Sample-size": ["A"], "Intervention-general": ["A"], "Duration": ["A"], "Intensity": ["A"], "Outcomes-general": ["A"], "Effect-strength": ["A"], "Adverse-effects": ["A"], "Conclusion-general": ["D"]}}, "id": "NEJMoa0907413_3R8YZBNQ9I37ZWCZDS5NHASYBGYQ7U", "children": [{"Answer": "A 2009 influenza pandemic was attributed to a novel influenza.  Researchers in Australia conducted research to find a safe and effective vaccine.  A total of 240 subjects were split into two groups and administered either 15 or 30 units of a potential vaccine.  After 21 days they were given the same dose again.  There were no deaths o serious side effects in any of the subjects.  Researchers determined that a dose of 15 units was sufficient to protect against the novel influenza strain.", "AssignmentId": "3COPXFW7XCXAUZI4W9F7LA7ACDBPKP", "Question": "NEJMoa0907413", "WorkerId": "A1LKDOJ1P1JFH4", "Qualification": 0.75, "Topic": "immunization", "Hop": 1, "Education": "College", "Gender": "male", "Age": "40-60", "level": 2, "branch": "NEJMoa0907413", "Tagging": {"Coarse": {"240": ["Participants"], "21": ["Intervention"], "australia": ["Participants"]}, "Fine": {"240": ["Sample-size"], "21": ["Duration"], "australia": ["Location"]}}, "Doggos_crowd": {"Coarse": {"Participants": ["C", "C", "B", "A"], "Intervention": ["A", "A", "A"], "Outcomes": ["A", "C", "C"], "Conclusion": ["A"]}, "Fine": {"Age": ["C"], "Condition": ["C"], "Location": ["B"], "Sample-size": ["A"], "Intervention-general": ["A"], "Duration": ["A"], "Intensity": ["A"], "Outcomes-general": ["A"], "Effect-strength": ["C"], "Adverse-effects": ["C"], "Conclusion-general": ["A"]}}, "id": "NEJMoa0907413_3COPXFW7XCXAUZI4W9F7LA7ACDBPKP", "children": [{"Answer": "A trial evaluating 2 doses of inactivated split virus 2009 H1N1 vaccine in 240 healthy adults between the ages of 18 to 64 in Australia showed a single 15ug dose was immunogenic in adults with mild to moderate vaccine associated reactions.", "AssignmentId": "37Q970SNZFT51QCAGGDJB0GMQ4US17", "Question": "NEJMoa0907413", "WorkerId": "A98E8M4QLI9RS", "Qualification": 0.75, "Topic": "immunization", "Hop": 2, "Education": "Some College", "Gender": "female", "Age": "40-60", "level": 3, "branch": "NEJMoa0907413", "Tagging": {"Coarse": {"240": ["Participants"], "healthy": ["Participants"], "adult": ["Participants"], "australia": ["Participants"], "2009 h1n1 vaccine": ["Intervention"]}, "Fine": {"240": ["Sample-size"], "healthy": ["Condition"], "adult": ["Age"], "australia": ["Location"], "2009 h1n1 vaccine": ["Intervention-general"]}}, "Doggos_crowd": {"Coarse": {"Participants": ["A", "A", "B", "A"], "Intervention": ["A", "C", "B"], "Outcomes": ["A", "C", "B"], "Conclusion": ["A"]}, "Fine": {"Age": ["A"], "Condition": ["A"], "Location": ["B"], "Sample-size": ["A"], "Intervention-general": ["A"], "Duration": ["C"], "Intensity": ["B"], "Outcomes-general": ["A"], "Effect-strength": ["C"], "Adverse-effects": ["B"], "Conclusion-general": ["A"]}}, "id": "NEJMoa0907413_37Q970SNZFT51QCAGGDJB0GMQ4US17", "children": [{"Answer": "A study of 2009 influenza A (H1N1) vaccine found a single 15-ug does was immunogenic in adults and had only mild-to-moderate reactions.", "AssignmentId": "3LOTDFNYA8KPYMNR7K25XRN1YTVWFI", "Question": "NEJMoa0907413", "WorkerId": "A2YTQDLACTLIBA", "Qualification": 0.875, "Topic": "immunization", "Hop": 3, "Education": "College", "Gender": "female", "Age": "60+", "level": 4, "branch": "NEJMoa0907413", "Tagging": {"Coarse": {"adult": ["Participants"]}, "Fine": {"adult": ["Age"]}}, "Doggos_crowd": {"Coarse": {"Participants": ["B", "C", "C", "C"], "Intervention": ["A", "B", "C"], "Outcomes": ["A", "B", "C"], "Conclusion": ["A"]}, "Fine": {"Age": ["B"], "Condition": ["C"], "Location": ["C"], "Sample-size": ["C"], "Intervention-general": ["A"], "Duration": ["C"], "Intensity": ["B"], "Outcomes-general": ["A"], "Effect-strength": ["C"], "Adverse-effects": ["B"], "Conclusion-general": ["A"]}}, "id": "NEJMoa0907413_3LOTDFNYA8KPYMNR7K25XRN1YTVWFI", "children": [{"Answer": "The H1N1 vaccine results in mild-moderate reactions.", "AssignmentId": "3JW0YLFXRU1R989MX9C51F91TZVWWW", "Question": "NEJMoa0907413", "WorkerId": "A25AJ66CYVUTBR", "Qualification": 0.625, "Topic": "immunization", "Hop": 4, "Education": "College", "Gender": "female", "Age": "40-60", "level": 5, "branch": "NEJMoa0907413", "Tagging": {"Coarse": {}, "Fine": {}}, "Doggos_crowd": {"Coarse": {"Participants": ["C", "C", "C", "C"], "Intervention": ["B", "C", "C"], "Outcomes": ["B", "C", "C"], "Conclusion": ["B"]}, "Fine": {"Age": ["C"], "Condition": ["C"], "Location": ["C"], "Sample-size": ["C"], "Intervention-general": ["B"], "Duration": ["C"], "Intensity": ["C"], "Outcomes-general": ["C"], "Effect-strength": ["C"], "Adverse-effects": ["B"], "Conclusion-general": ["B"]}}, "id": "NEJMoa0907413_3JW0YLFXRU1R989MX9C51F91TZVWWW"}]}]}]}]}, {"Answer": "A new influenza A virus is the reason for a recent influenza pandemic. In order to create an appropriate vaccine, a group trial in healthy adults will be conducted in Australia. &#13;The study was split into two groups: one that received more of the injection than the other. Different measurements were then taken after three weeks. This was done to evaluate the immunogenicity and safety of the vaccine after the doses. &#13;Three weeks after the first vaccine was administered, it was found that 95% of the recipients who had received the lower dosage had appropriate levels. Of those who received the higher dose, 89.1% had appropriate levels. Similar findings were reported after the second vaccine administration. No serious adverse symptoms were reported, however, 56.3% of recipients reported local discomfort and 53.8% of recipients reported systemic symptoms.&#13;This concludes that a single dose of the lesser amount is immunogenic in adults. ", "AssignmentId": "3TE3O85731T0PWUTKVDSQ9LVWML2RY", "Question": "NEJMoa0907413", "WorkerId": "A3P3ST7ED4JQCK", "Qualification": 0.875, "Topic": "immunization", "Hop": 0, "Education": "Some College", "Gender": "female", "Age": "15-24", "level": 1, "branch": "NEJMoa0907413", "Tagging": {"Coarse": {"immunogenicity": ["Outcomes"], "healthy": ["Participants"], "adult": ["Participants"], "89.1 %": ["Outcomes"], "local discomfort": ["Outcomes"], "systemic symptom": ["Outcomes"], "australia": ["Participants"]}, "Fine": {"immunogenicity": ["Outcomes-general"], "healthy": ["Condition"], "adult": ["Age"], "89.1 %": ["Effect-strength"], "local discomfort": ["Adverse-effects"], "systemic symptom": ["Adverse-effects"], "australia": ["Location"]}}, "Doggos_crowd": {"Coarse": {"Participants": ["B", "B", "A", "C"], "Intervention": ["B", "A", "B"], "Outcomes": ["A", "B", "A"], "Conclusion": ["A"]}, "Fine": {"Age": ["B"], "Condition": ["A"], "Location": ["B"], "Sample-size": ["C"], "Intervention-general": ["B"], "Duration": ["A"], "Intensity": ["B"], "Outcomes-general": ["A"], "Effect-strength": ["B"], "Adverse-effects": ["A"], "Conclusion-general": ["A"]}}, "id": "NEJMoa0907413_3TE3O85731T0PWUTKVDSQ9LVWML2RY", "children": [{"Answer": "In adults, one dose of 2009 H1N1 inactivated split virus vaccine effectively instigates an immune response to protect against influenza. Both the safety of the vaccine and the effectiveness on the immune system were studied in 240 subjects broken up into two age groups and then further broken down into a dose group of 15-ug and a dose group of 30-ug. 114 of the 120 subjects reflected antibody titers of greater than or equal to 1:40 in the 15-ug dose group. The 30-ug dose group reflected 106 of the 119 subjects to have titers of 1:40 or more. ", "AssignmentId": "30JNVC0ORA54SLIBQ1RZ8NHSPSQQHA", "Question": "NEJMoa0907413", "WorkerId": "ADGH08WUP68ZF", "Qualification": 0.75, "Topic": "immunization", "Hop": 1, "Education": "Some College", "Gender": "female", "Age": "15-24", "level": 2, "branch": "NEJMoa0907413", "Tagging": {"Coarse": {"240": ["Participants"], "adult": ["Participants"]}, "Fine": {"240": ["Sample-size"], "adult": ["Age"]}}, "Doggos_crowd": {"Coarse": {"Participants": ["B", "C", "C", "A"], "Intervention": ["A", "C", "A"], "Outcomes": ["A", "A", "C"], "Conclusion": ["C"]}, "Fine": {"Age": ["B"], "Condition": ["C"], "Location": ["C"], "Sample-size": ["A"], "Intervention-general": ["A"], "Duration": ["C"], "Intensity": ["A"], "Outcomes-general": ["A"], "Effect-strength": ["A"], "Adverse-effects": ["C"], "Conclusion-general": ["C"]}}, "id": "NEJMoa0907413_30JNVC0ORA54SLIBQ1RZ8NHSPSQQHA", "children": [{"Answer": "A study on safety and imunogenicity of 2009 Influenza A (H1N1) vaccine was performed showing no deaths or serious side-effects on 240 subjects. Local discomfort was reported by 56.3% of subjects on injection-site, and systemic symptoms like headache reported by 53.8%.", "AssignmentId": "30MVJZJNHNYURSWFXZJYY57ISYB9JP", "Question": "NEJMoa0907413", "WorkerId": "AISNLDPD2DFEG", "Qualification": 0.75, "Topic": "immunization", "Hop": 2, "Education": "College", "Gender": "female", "Age": "40-60", "level": 3, "branch": "NEJMoa0907413", "Tagging": {"Coarse": {"240": ["Participants"], "local discomfort": ["Outcomes"], "systemic symptom": ["Outcomes"]}, "Fine": {"240": ["Sample-size"], "local discomfort": ["Adverse-effects"], "systemic symptom": ["Adverse-effects"]}}, "Doggos_crowd": {"Coarse": {"Participants": ["C", "C", "C", "A"], "Intervention": ["A", "C", "C"], "Outcomes": ["A", "C", "A"], "Conclusion": ["B"]}, "Fine": {"Age": ["C"], "Condition": ["C"], "Location": ["C"], "Sample-size": ["A"], "Intervention-general": ["A"], "Duration": ["C"], "Intensity": ["C"], "Outcomes-general": ["A"], "Effect-strength": ["C"], "Adverse-effects": ["A"], "Conclusion-general": ["B"]}}, "id": "NEJMoa0907413_30MVJZJNHNYURSWFXZJYY57ISYB9JP", "children": [{"Answer": "240 adults receiving 2 doses of either 15 or 30 ug flu vaccines 21 days apart showed the 15 ug dose to be effective in 95% of subjects.  ", "AssignmentId": "3C6FJU71TREI69FHHAFS4O9KJOAYUI", "Question": "NEJMoa0907413", "WorkerId": "A3QEJSGOH50D8L", "Qualification": 0.875, "Topic": "immunization", "Hop": 3, "Education": "Some College", "Gender": "female", "Age": "24-39", "level": 4, "branch": "NEJMoa0907413", "Tagging": {"Coarse": {"240": ["Participants"], "adult": ["Participants"], "21": ["Intervention"]}, "Fine": {"240": ["Sample-size"], "adult": ["Age"], "21": ["Duration"]}}, "Doggos_crowd": {"Coarse": {"Participants": ["B", "C", "C", "A"], "Intervention": ["B", "B", "A"], "Outcomes": ["B", "B", "C"], "Conclusion": ["B"]}, "Fine": {"Age": ["B"], "Condition": ["C"], "Location": ["C"], "Sample-size": ["A"], "Intervention-general": ["B"], "Duration": ["B"], "Intensity": ["A"], "Outcomes-general": ["B"], "Effect-strength": ["B"], "Adverse-effects": ["C"], "Conclusion-general": ["B"]}}, "id": "NEJMoa0907413_3C6FJU71TREI69FHHAFS4O9KJOAYUI", "children": [{"Answer": "The H1N1 vaccine was immunogenic in adults with a single 15-ug dose.", "AssignmentId": "3JCG6DTRV4BH5EHE9RETH19THXYQQJ", "Question": "NEJMoa0907413", "WorkerId": "A2ELH7YDLFNJUZ", "Qualification": 0.875, "Topic": "immunization", "Hop": 4, "Education": "College", "Gender": "male", "Age": "24-39", "level": 5, "branch": "NEJMoa0907413", "Tagging": {"Coarse": {"adult": ["Participants"]}, "Fine": {"adult": ["Age"]}}, "Doggos_crowd": {"Coarse": {"Participants": ["B", "C", "C", "C"], "Intervention": ["B", "C", "B"], "Outcomes": ["A", "C", "C"], "Conclusion": ["B"]}, "Fine": {"Age": ["B"], "Condition": ["C"], "Location": ["C"], "Sample-size": ["C"], "Intervention-general": ["B"], "Duration": ["C"], "Intensity": ["B"], "Outcomes-general": ["A"], "Effect-strength": ["C"], "Adverse-effects": ["C"], "Conclusion-general": ["B"]}}, "id": "NEJMoa0907413_3JCG6DTRV4BH5EHE9RETH19THXYQQJ"}]}]}]}]}, {"Answer": "A study is currently being conducted in Australia on an inactivated H1N1 (2009) split virus vaccine and the effects on adults that are considered healthy from ages 18 to 64. 240 participants were separated into groups based on age, one being 50 years and greater with the other being less then 50 years old. Participants in each group were then randomly chosen for a dose of 15-ug or a dose of 30-ug given via intramuscular injection of the hemagglutinin antigen. After 21 days of vaccination, 114 out of 120 or approximately 95% of participants given 15-ug dose showed antibody titers of 1:40. 106 out of 119 or approximately 89.1% of participants given the dose of 30-ug of the vaccine showed 1:40 antibody titers. A second trial dose of the vaccine was ran and the results were congruent with the initial results. The inactivated 2009 H1N1 virus vaccine proves to be immunogenic in healthy adults when given in a single dose of 15-ug. Only mild adverse effects were observed in around half of the participants in the study. ", "AssignmentId": "39N5ACM9HF8QD3ZDSCOIV1TU1BTP99", "Question": "NEJMoa0907413", "WorkerId": "ADGH08WUP68ZF", "Qualification": 0.75, "Topic": "immunization", "Hop": 0, "Education": "Some College", "Gender": "female", "Age": "15-24", "level": 1, "branch": "NEJMoa0907413", "Tagging": {"Coarse": {"240": ["Participants"], "healthy": ["Participants"], "adult": ["Participants"], "21": ["Intervention"], "89.1 %": ["Outcomes"], "australia": ["Participants"]}, "Fine": {"240": ["Sample-size"], "healthy": ["Condition"], "adult": ["Age"], "21": ["Duration"], "89.1 %": ["Effect-strength"], "australia": ["Location"]}}, "Doggos_crowd": {"Coarse": {"Participants": ["A", "A", "B", "A"], "Intervention": ["A", "A", "A"], "Outcomes": ["A", "A", "B"], "Conclusion": ["A"]}, "Fine": {"Age": ["A"], "Condition": ["A"], "Location": ["B"], "Sample-size": ["A"], "Intervention-general": ["A"], "Duration": ["A"], "Intensity": ["A"], "Outcomes-general": ["A"], "Effect-strength": ["A"], "Adverse-effects": ["B"], "Conclusion-general": ["A"]}}, "id": "NEJMoa0907413_39N5ACM9HF8QD3ZDSCOIV1TU1BTP99", "children": [{"Answer": "To develop a vaccine to address the 2009 H1N1 pandemic, a randomized, parallel-group trial that is evaluating two doses of inactivated, split-virus vaccine in health adults in ongoing.  Researchers looked at the immunogenicity and safety of the vaccine after 2 doses.  Participated received either 15 or 30 micrograms or hemagglutinin antigen.  Antibody titers were then measured 21 days after vaccination.  The results wee better for the 15 mg dose group.  Local discomfort and headache were the only adverse events reported.  ", "AssignmentId": "3NXNZ5RS1BI17XVDWQU1VF291PZ97E", "Question": "NEJMoa0907413", "WorkerId": "A3BDVHNMJECSKG", "Qualification": 0.5, "Topic": "immunization", "Hop": 1, "Education": "College", "Gender": "female", "Age": "24-39", "level": 2, "branch": "NEJMoa0907413", "Tagging": {"Coarse": {"immunogenicity": ["Outcomes"], "adult": ["Participants"], "21": ["Intervention"], "local discomfort": ["Outcomes"]}, "Fine": {"immunogenicity": ["Outcomes-general"], "adult": ["Age"], "21": ["Duration"], "local discomfort": ["Adverse-effects"]}}, "Doggos_crowd": {"Coarse": {"Participants": ["B", "C", "C", "C"], "Intervention": ["A", "A", "A"], "Outcomes": ["A", "C", "B"], "Conclusion": ["A"]}, "Fine": {"Age": ["B"], "Condition": ["C"], "Location": ["C"], "Sample-size": ["C"], "Intervention-general": ["A"], "Duration": ["A"], "Intensity": ["A"], "Outcomes-general": ["A"], "Effect-strength": ["C"], "Adverse-effects": ["B"], "Conclusion-general": ["A"]}}, "id": "NEJMoa0907413_3NXNZ5RS1BI17XVDWQU1VF291PZ97E", "children": [{"Answer": "As a result of the first influenza pandemic in 41 years, a trial was conducted, evaluating two doses of an H1N1 vaccine for immunogenicity and safety. It was concluded that a single dose of the smaller amount used in the trial was immunogeic and safe in adults.", "AssignmentId": "3D3VGR7TA10PAEQCOVRX9JQN2N03RZ", "Question": "NEJMoa0907413", "WorkerId": "AAB13RUHSABEV", "Qualification": 0.875, "Topic": "immunization", "Hop": 2, "Education": "College", "Gender": "female", "Age": "40-60", "level": 3, "branch": "NEJMoa0907413", "Tagging": {"Coarse": {"immunogenicity": ["Outcomes"], "adult": ["Participants"]}, "Fine": {"immunogenicity": ["Outcomes-general"], "adult": ["Age"]}}, "Doggos_crowd": {"Coarse": {"Participants": ["B", "C", "C", "C"], "Intervention": ["B", "C", "B"], "Outcomes": ["A", "C", "C"], "Conclusion": ["B"]}, "Fine": {"Age": ["B"], "Condition": ["C"], "Location": ["C"], "Sample-size": ["C"], "Intervention-general": ["B"], "Duration": ["C"], "Intensity": ["B"], "Outcomes-general": ["A"], "Effect-strength": ["C"], "Adverse-effects": ["C"], "Conclusion-general": ["B"]}}, "id": "NEJMoa0907413_3D3VGR7TA10PAEQCOVRX9JQN2N03RZ", "children": [{"Answer": "The H1N1 vaccine was studied for safety and immunogenicity. It was immunogenic in adults with mild/moderate vaccine related reactions.", "AssignmentId": "3Y9N9SS8LZWV94776UWD4U9JONOD3L", "Question": "NEJMoa0907413", "WorkerId": "AJITIN95JSBAR", "Qualification": 0.875, "Topic": "immunization", "Hop": 3, "Education": "College", "Gender": "male", "Age": "24-39", "level": 4, "branch": "NEJMoa0907413", "Tagging": {"Coarse": {"immunogenicity": ["Outcomes"], "adult": ["Participants"]}, "Fine": {"immunogenicity": ["Outcomes-general"], "adult": ["Age"]}}, "Doggos_crowd": {"Coarse": {"Participants": ["B", "C", "C", "C"], "Intervention": ["B", "C", "C"], "Outcomes": ["A", "C", "B"], "Conclusion": ["B"]}, "Fine": {"Age": ["B"], "Condition": ["C"], "Location": ["C"], "Sample-size": ["C"], "Intervention-general": ["B"], "Duration": ["C"], "Intensity": ["C"], "Outcomes-general": ["A"], "Effect-strength": ["C"], "Adverse-effects": ["B"], "Conclusion-general": ["B"]}}, "id": "NEJMoa0907413_3Y9N9SS8LZWV94776UWD4U9JONOD3L", "children": [{"Answer": "New vaccine with high efficacy has common side effects for H1N1", "AssignmentId": "3V26SBZTBEZZXYJWJJGJZNX1R34ZZG", "Question": "NEJMoa0907413", "WorkerId": "A3723CQM6I92CU", "Qualification": 0.625, "Topic": "immunization", "Hop": 4, "Education": "College", "Gender": "male", "Age": "15-24", "level": 5, "branch": "NEJMoa0907413", "Tagging": {"Coarse": {}, "Fine": {}}, "Doggos_crowd": {"Coarse": {"Participants": ["C", "C", "C", "C"], "Intervention": ["B", "C", "C"], "Outcomes": ["C", "C", "C"], "Conclusion": ["B"]}, "Fine": {"Age": ["C"], "Condition": ["C"], "Location": ["C"], "Sample-size": ["C"], "Intervention-general": ["B"], "Duration": ["C"], "Intensity": ["C"], "Outcomes-general": ["C"], "Effect-strength": ["C"], "Adverse-effects": ["C"], "Conclusion-general": ["B"]}}, "id": "NEJMoa0907413_3V26SBZTBEZZXYJWJJGJZNX1R34ZZG"}]}]}]}]}, {"Answer": "A randomized, observer-blind, parallel-group trial evaluating 2 doses of inactivated split virus 2009 H1N1 vaccine in healthy adults age 18 to 64 is ongoing at a site in Australia. The immunogenicity and safety of a vaccine was evaluated after each of 2 scheduled doses given 21 days apart. 240 subjects, equally divided into 2 age groups groups were enrolled and randomly received either 15 ug or 30 ug hemagglutinin antigen by IM injection. Antibody titers were measured at baseline and 21 days after vaccination. The coprimary immongenicity end points were the proportion of subjects w/ antibody titers of 1:40 or more on hemagglutination-inhibition assay, the proportion of subjects with either seroconversion or a significant increase in antibody titer &amp; the factor increase in the geometric mean titer. By day 21 after the 1st dose, antibody titers of 1:40 or more were observed in 114 of 120 subjects who received the 15ug does and in 106 of 119 subjects who received the 30ug dose. A single 15-us dose of 2009 H1N1 vaccine was immunogenic in adults with mild to moderate associated reactions.", "AssignmentId": "37TD41K0AIUPOTM8WD23SWZDUHBCS3", "Question": "NEJMoa0907413", "WorkerId": "A98E8M4QLI9RS", "Qualification": 0.75, "Topic": "immunization", "Hop": 0, "Education": "Some College", "Gender": "female", "Age": "40-60", "level": 1, "branch": "NEJMoa0907413", "Tagging": {"Coarse": {"immunogenicity": ["Outcomes"], "240": ["Participants"], "healthy": ["Participants"], "adult": ["Participants"], "21": ["Intervention"], "114 of 120": ["Outcomes"], "106 of 119": ["Outcomes"], "australia": ["Participants"], "2009 h1n1 vaccine": ["Intervention"]}, "Fine": {"immunogenicity": ["Outcomes-general"], "240": ["Sample-size"], "healthy": ["Condition"], "adult": ["Age"], "21": ["Duration"], "114 of 120": ["Effect-strength"], "106 of 119": ["Effect-strength"], "australia": ["Location"], "2009 h1n1 vaccine": ["Intervention-general"]}}, "Doggos_crowd": {"Coarse": {"Participants": ["A", "A", "A", "A"], "Intervention": ["A", "A", "A"], "Outcomes": ["A", "A", "C"], "Conclusion": ["A"]}, "Fine": {"Age": ["A"], "Condition": ["A"], "Location": ["A"], "Sample-size": ["A"], "Intervention-general": ["A"], "Duration": ["A"], "Intensity": ["A"], "Outcomes-general": ["A"], "Effect-strength": ["A"], "Adverse-effects": ["C"], "Conclusion-general": ["A"]}}, "id": "NEJMoa0907413_37TD41K0AIUPOTM8WD23SWZDUHBCS3", "children": [{"Answer": "In 2009, vaccines against the H1N1 strain of influenza were tested in Australia. Two doses of H1N1 vaccines were tested on patients between the ages of 18-64. The groups were split into age categories (over or under 50 years old) and received either the 15 or 30 ug dose of the vaccine in an injection. The antibody titers were tested after the first and second doses were administered. 95% of the 15 ug dose subjects showed titer reactions to the vaccine and 89.1% of subjects responded to the 30 ug dose. No serious vaccine reactions occurred.", "AssignmentId": "3M68NM076ISO7XDU7XPVGM27C0JR6I", "Question": "NEJMoa0907413", "WorkerId": "A6CVN7CSC1K26", "Qualification": 0.75, "Topic": "immunization", "Hop": 1, "Education": "College", "Gender": "female", "Age": "24-39", "level": 2, "branch": "NEJMoa0907413", "Tagging": {"Coarse": {"89.1 %": ["Outcomes"], "australia": ["Participants"]}, "Fine": {"89.1 %": ["Effect-strength"], "australia": ["Location"]}}, "Doggos_crowd": {"Coarse": {"Participants": ["A", "C", "B", "C"], "Intervention": ["A", "C", "A"], "Outcomes": ["B", "A", "C"], "Conclusion": ["B"]}, "Fine": {"Age": ["A"], "Condition": ["C"], "Location": ["B"], "Sample-size": ["C"], "Intervention-general": ["A"], "Duration": ["C"], "Intensity": ["A"], "Outcomes-general": ["B"], "Effect-strength": ["A"], "Adverse-effects": ["C"], "Conclusion-general": ["B"]}}, "id": "NEJMoa0907413_3M68NM076ISO7XDU7XPVGM27C0JR6I", "children": [{"Answer": "A single 15-ug dose of 2009 H1N1 (Influenza A) vaccine was immunogenic in adults in a study of 240 subjects.  There were no deaths and only mild-to-moderate vaccine-associated reactions (injection site tenderness or pain, headache).", "AssignmentId": "3A1PQ49WVI2GBHYU5M1K7M9KHUR1HB", "Question": "NEJMoa0907413", "WorkerId": "A2YTQDLACTLIBA", "Qualification": 0.875, "Topic": "immunization", "Hop": 2, "Education": "College", "Gender": "female", "Age": "60+", "level": 3, "branch": "NEJMoa0907413", "Tagging": {"Coarse": {"240": ["Participants"], "adult": ["Participants"]}, "Fine": {"240": ["Sample-size"], "adult": ["Age"]}}, "Doggos_crowd": {"Coarse": {"Participants": ["B", "C", "C", "A"], "Intervention": ["A", "B", "C"], "Outcomes": ["A", "C", "B"], "Conclusion": ["A"]}, "Fine": {"Age": ["B"], "Condition": ["C"], "Location": ["C"], "Sample-size": ["A"], "Intervention-general": ["A"], "Duration": ["C"], "Intensity": ["B"], "Outcomes-general": ["A"], "Effect-strength": ["C"], "Adverse-effects": ["B"], "Conclusion-general": ["A"]}}, "id": "NEJMoa0907413_3A1PQ49WVI2GBHYU5M1K7M9KHUR1HB", "children": [{"Answer": "The first influenza outbreak was caused by a flu virus was squashed by the introduction of the single dose H1N1 vaccine. ", "AssignmentId": "3BV8HQ2ZZXMW8GRD5M39LWDXDBWA6P", "Question": "NEJMoa0907413", "WorkerId": "A1AZV2XOQK7RSW", "Qualification": 0.875, "Topic": "immunization", "Hop": 3, "Education": "College", "Gender": "female", "Age": "40-60", "level": 4, "branch": "NEJMoa0907413", "Tagging": {"Coarse": {}, "Fine": {}}, "Doggos_crowd": {"Coarse": {"Participants": ["C", "C", "C", "C"], "Intervention": ["B", "C", "C"], "Outcomes": ["B", "C", "C"], "Conclusion": ["B"]}, "Fine": {"Age": ["C"], "Condition": ["C"], "Location": ["C"], "Sample-size": ["C"], "Intervention-general": ["B"], "Duration": ["C"], "Intensity": ["C"], "Outcomes-general": ["B"], "Effect-strength": ["C"], "Adverse-effects": ["C"], "Conclusion-general": ["B"]}}, "id": "NEJMoa0907413_3BV8HQ2ZZXMW8GRD5M39LWDXDBWA6P", "children": [{"Answer": "A single 15ug dose of 2009 H1H1 vaccine is immunogenic in adults.", "AssignmentId": "3WQ3B2KGE916K4V85UROLB6MNL51BN", "Question": "NEJMoa0907413", "WorkerId": "A98E8M4QLI9RS", "Qualification": 0.75, "Topic": "immunization", "Hop": 4, "Education": "Some College", "Gender": "female", "Age": "40-60", "level": 5, "branch": "NEJMoa0907413", "Tagging": {"Coarse": {"adult": ["Participants"]}, "Fine": {"adult": ["Age"]}}, "Doggos_crowd": {"Coarse": {"Participants": ["C", "C", "C", "C"], "Intervention": ["A", "B", "C"], "Outcomes": ["A", "C", "C"], "Conclusion": ["A"]}, "Fine": {"Age": ["C"], "Condition": ["C"], "Location": ["C"], "Sample-size": ["C"], "Intervention-general": ["A"], "Duration": ["C"], "Intensity": ["B"], "Outcomes-general": ["A"], "Effect-strength": ["C"], "Adverse-effects": ["C"], "Conclusion-general": ["A"]}}, "id": "NEJMoa0907413_3WQ3B2KGE916K4V85UROLB6MNL51BN"}]}]}]}]}, {"Answer": "A new influenza A virus (H1N1) has caused the first influenza pandemic in 41 years, therefore a safe and effective vaccine is needed. A randomized group trial evaluating two doses of an inactivated, split-virus 2009 H1N1 vaccine in healthy adults is ongoing at a single site in Australia. The immunogenicity and safety of the vaccine was evaluated after each of two scheduled doses, administered 21 days apart to a total of 240 subjects, equally divided into two age groups (under 50 and over 50). The subjects randomly received either a lower dosage or a higher dosage of the vaccine. By day 21 after the first dose, antibody titers of 1:40 or more were observed in 95 percent of the subjects who received the lower dosage, and 89.1 percent of the subjects who received the higher dosage. A similar result was observed after the second dose of vaccine. Only local discomfort and milt to moderate systemic symptoms were reported. Conclustion: single lower dose of 2009 H1N1 was immunogenic in adults, with mild-to-moderate vaccine related reactions.", "AssignmentId": "3HUTX6F6VV8XSJ2DS3WOWEGQL392O5", "Question": "NEJMoa0907413", "WorkerId": "AAB13RUHSABEV", "Qualification": 0.875, "Topic": "immunization", "Hop": 0, "Education": "College", "Gender": "female", "Age": "40-60", "level": 1, "branch": "NEJMoa0907413", "Tagging": {"Coarse": {"immunogenicity": ["Outcomes"], "240": ["Participants"], "healthy": ["Participants"], "adult": ["Participants"], "21": ["Intervention"], "local discomfort": ["Outcomes"], "systemic symptom": ["Outcomes"], "australia": ["Participants"], "2009 h1n1 vaccine": ["Intervention"]}, "Fine": {"immunogenicity": ["Outcomes-general"], "240": ["Sample-size"], "healthy": ["Condition"], "adult": ["Age"], "21": ["Duration"], "local discomfort": ["Adverse-effects"], "systemic symptom": ["Adverse-effects"], "australia": ["Location"], "2009 h1n1 vaccine": ["Intervention-general"]}}, "Doggos_crowd": {"Coarse": {"Participants": ["B", "A", "A", "A"], "Intervention": ["A", "A", "B"], "Outcomes": ["A", "A", "B"], "Conclusion": ["A"]}, "Fine": {"Age": ["B"], "Condition": ["A"], "Location": ["A"], "Sample-size": ["A"], "Intervention-general": ["A"], "Duration": ["A"], "Intensity": ["B"], "Outcomes-general": ["A"], "Effect-strength": ["A"], "Adverse-effects": ["B"], "Conclusion-general": ["A"]}}, "id": "NEJMoa0907413_3HUTX6F6VV8XSJ2DS3WOWEGQL392O5", "children": [{"Answer": "Single 15-ug dose of 2009 H1N1 vaccine was evaluated for safety and immunogenicity and found to be immunogenic in adults with mild-to-moderate vaccine-associated reactions.  The vaccine was a split-virus 2009 H1N1 vaccine and was administered to healthy adults 18-64 in Australia.  No deaths or serious adverse effects were reported.  Tenderness/pain at injection site was reported by 56.3%, headache by 53.8% after each dose and nearly all were mild to moderate in intensit.", "AssignmentId": "3YT88D1N09J3NADHYBI087497HJ3KR", "Question": "NEJMoa0907413", "WorkerId": "A2YTQDLACTLIBA", "Qualification": 0.875, "Topic": "immunization", "Hop": 1, "Education": "College", "Gender": "female", "Age": "60+", "level": 2, "branch": "NEJMoa0907413", "Tagging": {"Coarse": {"immunogenicity": ["Outcomes"], "healthy": ["Participants"], "adult": ["Participants"], "australia": ["Participants"], "2009 h1n1 vaccine": ["Intervention"]}, "Fine": {"immunogenicity": ["Outcomes-general"], "healthy": ["Condition"], "adult": ["Age"], "australia": ["Location"], "2009 h1n1 vaccine": ["Intervention-general"]}}, "Doggos_crowd": {"Coarse": {"Participants": ["A", "A", "B", "C"], "Intervention": ["A", "B", "C"], "Outcomes": ["A", "C", "A"], "Conclusion": ["A"]}, "Fine": {"Age": ["A"], "Condition": ["A"], "Location": ["B"], "Sample-size": ["C"], "Intervention-general": ["A"], "Duration": ["C"], "Intensity": ["B"], "Outcomes-general": ["A"], "Effect-strength": ["C"], "Adverse-effects": ["A"], "Conclusion-general": ["A"]}}, "id": "NEJMoa0907413_3YT88D1N09J3NADHYBI087497HJ3KR", "children": [{"Answer": "2009 influenza A (H1N1) virus was the first influenza pandemic in 41 years. Therefore a safe and effective vaccine is needed. A single 15- ug dose of 2009 H1N1 vaccine was immunogenic in adults, with mild-to-moderate vaccine-associated reactions.", "AssignmentId": "3G5W44VEU834HMP5TQPKR1TIC14GKN", "Question": "NEJMoa0907413", "WorkerId": "A2ELH7YDLFNJUZ", "Qualification": 0.875, "Topic": "immunization", "Hop": 2, "Education": "College", "Gender": "male", "Age": "24-39", "level": 3, "branch": "NEJMoa0907413", "Tagging": {"Coarse": {"adult": ["Participants"], "2009 h1n1 vaccine": ["Intervention"]}, "Fine": {"adult": ["Age"], "2009 h1n1 vaccine": ["Intervention-general"]}}, "Doggos_crowd": {"Coarse": {"Participants": ["B", "C", "C", "C"], "Intervention": ["A", "C", "B"], "Outcomes": ["A", "B", "C"], "Conclusion": ["A"]}, "Fine": {"Age": ["B"], "Condition": ["C"], "Location": ["C"], "Sample-size": ["C"], "Intervention-general": ["A"], "Duration": ["C"], "Intensity": ["B"], "Outcomes-general": ["A"], "Effect-strength": ["C"], "Adverse-effects": ["B"], "Conclusion-general": ["A"]}}, "id": "NEJMoa0907413_3G5W44VEU834HMP5TQPKR1TIC14GKN", "children": [{"Answer": "A single 15-ug dose of 2009 H1N1 vaccine turned out to be immunogenic in adults with mild-to-moderate vaccine-associated reactions.", "AssignmentId": "33IZTU6J82MDRRX3N9YQ69KNWL4SXZ", "Question": "NEJMoa0907413", "WorkerId": "A2ELH7YDLFNJUZ", "Qualification": 0.875, "Topic": "immunization", "Hop": 3, "Education": "College", "Gender": "male", "Age": "24-39", "level": 4, "branch": "NEJMoa0907413", "Tagging": {"Coarse": {"adult": ["Participants"], "2009 h1n1 vaccine": ["Intervention"]}, "Fine": {"adult": ["Age"], "2009 h1n1 vaccine": ["Intervention-general"]}}, "Doggos_crowd": {"Coarse": {"Participants": ["B", "C", "C", "C"], "Intervention": ["A", "B", "C"], "Outcomes": ["A", "B", "C"], "Conclusion": ["A"]}, "Fine": {"Age": ["B"], "Condition": ["C"], "Location": ["C"], "Sample-size": ["C"], "Intervention-general": ["A"], "Duration": ["C"], "Intensity": ["B"], "Outcomes-general": ["A"], "Effect-strength": ["C"], "Adverse-effects": ["B"], "Conclusion-general": ["A"]}}, "id": "NEJMoa0907413_33IZTU6J82MDRRX3N9YQ69KNWL4SXZ", "children": [{"Answer": "Successful H1N1 vaccine tests were completed in Australia.", "AssignmentId": "3KMS4QQVK3BY3MTAI6J29GT6BPYKFS", "Question": "NEJMoa0907413", "WorkerId": "A1KR3HNLXSLC10", "Qualification": 0.875, "Topic": "immunization", "Hop": 4, "Education": "Some College", "Gender": "male", "Age": "24-39", "level": 5, "branch": "NEJMoa0907413", "Tagging": {"Coarse": {"australia": ["Participants"]}, "Fine": {"australia": ["Location"]}}, "Doggos_crowd": {"Coarse": {"Participants": ["C", "C", "B", "C"], "Intervention": ["B", "C", "C"], "Outcomes": ["C", "C", "C"], "Conclusion": ["B"]}, "Fine": {"Age": ["C"], "Condition": ["C"], "Location": ["B"], "Sample-size": ["C"], "Intervention-general": ["B"], "Duration": ["C"], "Intensity": ["C"], "Outcomes-general": ["C"], "Effect-strength": ["C"], "Adverse-effects": ["C"], "Conclusion-general": ["B"]}}, "id": "NEJMoa0907413_3KMS4QQVK3BY3MTAI6J29GT6BPYKFS"}]}]}]}]}, {"Answer": "This describes a study in which they are attempted to test a novel vaccine against the 2009 influenza H1N1. The study evaluated the immunogenicity and safety of the vaccine after each of two scheduled doses. Subjects were at a single site in Australia, and were divided into two age groups (less than or over 50 years old) and randomly received ether 15ug or 30ug of hemagglutinin antigen intramuscularly. By 21 days after the first dose, antibody titers of 1:40 or more were found in 95.0% of subjects receiving the 15ug dose and 89.1% of subjects receiving the 30ug dose. A similar result was seen after the second dose of vaccine. No deaths, serious adverse events, or adverse events of interest were reported. About half of subjects described local discomfort at the site of injection, and about half reported mild to moderate systemic symptoms (headaches, etc). Thus, a single 15ug dose of 2009 H1N1 vaccine was immunogenic in adults with mild-to-moderate vaccine-associated reactions.", "AssignmentId": "3S96KQ6I9NP08L51L924M7DHH4HDTH", "Question": "NEJMoa0907413", "WorkerId": "A3LW4YHAM1JH1X", "Qualification": 0.875, "Topic": "immunization", "Hop": 0, "Education": "College", "Gender": "male", "Age": "24-39", "level": 1, "branch": "NEJMoa0907413", "Tagging": {"Coarse": {"immunogenicity": ["Outcomes"], "adult": ["Participants"], "21": ["Intervention"], "95.0 %": ["Outcomes"], "89.1 %": ["Outcomes"], "local discomfort": ["Outcomes"], "systemic symptom": ["Outcomes"], "australia": ["Participants"], "2009 h1n1 vaccine": ["Intervention"]}, "Fine": {"immunogenicity": ["Outcomes-general"], "adult": ["Age"], "21": ["Duration"], "95.0 %": ["Effect-strength"], "89.1 %": ["Effect-strength"], "local discomfort": ["Adverse-effects"], "systemic symptom": ["Adverse-effects"], "australia": ["Location"], "2009 h1n1 vaccine": ["Intervention-general"]}}, "Doggos_crowd": {"Coarse": {"Participants": ["B", "C", "A", "C"], "Intervention": ["A", "A", "A"], "Outcomes": ["A", "A", "B"], "Conclusion": ["A"]}, "Fine": {"Age": ["B"], "Condition": ["C"], "Location": ["A"], "Sample-size": ["C"], "Intervention-general": ["A"], "Duration": ["A"], "Intensity": ["A"], "Outcomes-general": ["A"], "Effect-strength": ["A"], "Adverse-effects": ["B"], "Conclusion-general": ["A"]}}, "id": "NEJMoa0907413_3S96KQ6I9NP08L51L924M7DHH4HDTH", "children": [{"Answer": "In a random, observer blind, parallel group trial evaluating 2 doses of an inactivated, split virus 2009 H1N1 vaccine, a single 15-ug dose was found to be immunogenic in adults, with mild to moderate vaccine associated reactions. Healthy adults between the ages of 18 and 64 years were given 2 doses of the vaccine, scheduled 21 days apart. There were 240 subjects divided equally into 2 age groups, 50 years and &lt;  50 years of age.  Antibody titers were measured at baseline and at 21 days after vaccination to determine results.", "AssignmentId": "30LB5CDZNDV2VDD6FP3RTOUF8FZ0Z4", "Question": "NEJMoa0907413", "WorkerId": "AON59V5VZU2AK", "Qualification": 0.5, "Topic": "immunization", "Hop": 1, "Education": "College", "Gender": "female", "Age": "40-60", "level": 2, "branch": "NEJMoa0907413", "Tagging": {"Coarse": {"240": ["Participants"], "healthy": ["Participants"], "adult": ["Participants"], "18 and 64": ["Participants"], "21": ["Intervention"], "2009 h1n1 vaccine": ["Intervention"]}, "Fine": {"240": ["Sample-size"], "healthy": ["Condition"], "adult": ["Age"], "18 and 64": ["Age"], "21": ["Duration"], "2009 h1n1 vaccine": ["Intervention-general"]}}, "Doggos_crowd": {"Coarse": {"Participants": ["A", "A", "C", "A"], "Intervention": ["A", "A", "B"], "Outcomes": ["A", "B", "B"], "Conclusion": ["A"]}, "Fine": {"Age": ["A"], "Condition": ["A"], "Location": ["C"], "Sample-size": ["A"], "Intervention-general": ["A"], "Duration": ["A"], "Intensity": ["B"], "Outcomes-general": ["A"], "Effect-strength": ["B"], "Adverse-effects": ["B"], "Conclusion-general": ["A"]}}, "id": "NEJMoa0907413_30LB5CDZNDV2VDD6FP3RTOUF8FZ0Z4", "children": [{"Answer": "This study showed that a single 15-ug dose of the 2009 H1N1 virus is responsible for the first outbreak in years. The need for a new vaccine arose and was studied for these results. The dose was shown effective in adults at the end.", "AssignmentId": "3CP1TO84PUMBK9WVNO0PN8GZ5S652A", "Question": "NEJMoa0907413", "WorkerId": "A1AZV2XOQK7RSW", "Qualification": 0.875, "Topic": "immunization", "Hop": 2, "Education": "College", "Gender": "female", "Age": "40-60", "level": 3, "branch": "NEJMoa0907413", "Tagging": {"Coarse": {"adult": ["Participants"]}, "Fine": {"adult": ["Age"]}}, "Doggos_crowd": {"Coarse": {"Participants": ["B", "C", "C", "C"], "Intervention": ["A", "B", "C"], "Outcomes": ["C", "C", "C"], "Conclusion": ["B"]}, "Fine": {"Age": ["B"], "Condition": ["C"], "Location": ["C"], "Sample-size": ["C"], "Intervention-general": ["A"], "Duration": ["C"], "Intensity": ["B"], "Outcomes-general": ["C"], "Effect-strength": ["C"], "Adverse-effects": ["C"], "Conclusion-general": ["B"]}}, "id": "NEJMoa0907413_3CP1TO84PUMBK9WVNO0PN8GZ5S652A", "children": [{"Answer": "Influenza A, the ( H1N1 ) virus caused a pandemic. 15-&#956;g of 2009 H1N1 vaccine was responsive in adults with mild side effects.", "AssignmentId": "3IAEQB9FMF5S029VGE7F9RKGMGRWDJ", "Question": "NEJMoa0907413", "WorkerId": "A3P57IUDHUKNCE", "Qualification": 0.75, "Topic": "immunization", "Hop": 3, "Education": "Some College", "Gender": "male", "Age": "24-39", "level": 4, "branch": "NEJMoa0907413", "Tagging": {"Coarse": {"adult": ["Participants"], "2009 h1n1 vaccine": ["Intervention"]}, "Fine": {"adult": ["Age"], "2009 h1n1 vaccine": ["Intervention-general"]}}, "Doggos_crowd": {"Coarse": {"Participants": ["B", "C", "C", "C"], "Intervention": ["A", "B", "C"], "Outcomes": ["B", "B", "C"], "Conclusion": ["A"]}, "Fine": {"Age": ["B"], "Condition": ["C"], "Location": ["C"], "Sample-size": ["C"], "Intervention-general": ["A"], "Duration": ["C"], "Intensity": ["B"], "Outcomes-general": ["B"], "Effect-strength": ["C"], "Adverse-effects": ["B"], "Conclusion-general": ["A"]}}, "id": "NEJMoa0907413_3IAEQB9FMF5S029VGE7F9RKGMGRWDJ", "children": [{"Answer": "A single 15 ug dose of 2009 H1N1 vaccine was effective in adults.", "AssignmentId": "3PZDLQMM0U6WJU5A2YNX1EM9XCM2CF", "Question": "NEJMoa0907413", "WorkerId": "AON59V5VZU2AK", "Qualification": 0.5, "Topic": "immunization", "Hop": 4, "Education": "College", "Gender": "female", "Age": "40-60", "level": 5, "branch": "NEJMoa0907413", "Tagging": {"Coarse": {"adult": ["Participants"], "2009 h1n1 vaccine": ["Intervention"]}, "Fine": {"adult": ["Age"], "2009 h1n1 vaccine": ["Intervention-general"]}}, "Doggos_crowd": {"Coarse": {"Participants": ["B", "C", "C", "C"], "Intervention": ["A", "C", "B"], "Outcomes": ["B", "C", "C"], "Conclusion": ["A"]}, "Fine": {"Age": ["B"], "Condition": ["C"], "Location": ["C"], "Sample-size": ["C"], "Intervention-general": ["A"], "Duration": ["C"], "Intensity": ["B"], "Outcomes-general": ["B"], "Effect-strength": ["C"], "Adverse-effects": ["C"], "Conclusion-general": ["A"]}}, "id": "NEJMoa0907413_3PZDLQMM0U6WJU5A2YNX1EM9XCM2CF"}]}]}]}]}, {"Answer": "A study was done in Australia to evaluate the immunogenicity and safety of the 2009 Influenza A (H1N1) vaccine after each of two scheduled doses, administered 21 days apart. A total of 240 healthy adults between the ages of 18 and 64 years old were divided equally into two age groups (&lt; 50 years and &gt; or = 50 years), and underwent randomization to receive either 15 ug or 30 ug of hemagglutinin antigen by intramuscular injection. By day 21 after the first dose, antibody titers of 1:40 or more were observed in 114 of 120 subjects (95.0 %) who received the 15 ug dose and in 106 of 119 subjects (89.1 %) who received the 30 ug dose. A similar result was observed after the second dose of the vaccine. No deaths, serious adverse events, or adverse events of special interest were reported. Local discomfort such as injection-site tenderness or pain was reported by 56.3 % of the subjects. Overall, a single 15 ug dose of 2009 HnN1 vaccine was immunogenic in adults.", "AssignmentId": "37W3JXSD67TVYD4MCAUTMCUH3M3WYW", "Question": "NEJMoa0907413", "WorkerId": "A3D8ZG1VV5FO35", "Qualification": 0.875, "Topic": "immunization", "Hop": 0, "Education": "College", "Gender": "female", "Age": "40-60", "level": 1, "branch": "NEJMoa0907413", "Tagging": {"Coarse": {"hemagglutinin antigen by intramuscular injection": ["Intervention"], "immunogenicity": ["Outcomes"], "240": ["Participants"], "healthy": ["Participants"], "adult": ["Participants"], "18 and 64": ["Participants"], "21": ["Intervention"], "114 of 120": ["Outcomes"], "95.0 %": ["Outcomes"], "106 of 119": ["Outcomes"], "89.1 %": ["Outcomes"], "local discomfort": ["Outcomes"], "australia": ["Participants"]}, "Fine": {"immunogenicity": ["Outcomes-general"], "240": ["Sample-size"], "healthy": ["Condition"], "adult": ["Age"], "18 and 64": ["Age"], "21": ["Duration"], "114 of 120": ["Effect-strength"], "95.0 %": ["Effect-strength"], "106 of 119": ["Effect-strength"], "89.1 %": ["Effect-strength"], "local discomfort": ["Adverse-effects"], "australia": ["Location"]}}, "Doggos_crowd": {"Coarse": {"Participants": ["A", "A", "B", "A"], "Intervention": ["A", "A", "A"], "Outcomes": ["A", "A", "B"], "Conclusion": ["A"]}, "Fine": {"Age": ["A"], "Condition": ["A"], "Location": ["B"], "Sample-size": ["A"], "Intervention-general": ["A"], "Duration": ["A"], "Intensity": ["A"], "Outcomes-general": ["A"], "Effect-strength": ["A"], "Adverse-effects": ["B"], "Conclusion-general": ["A"]}}, "id": "NEJMoa0907413_37W3JXSD67TVYD4MCAUTMCUH3M3WYW", "children": [{"Answer": "240 subjects participated in this study divided into two groups. Ages 50+ and below 50. They randomly received either 15 or 30 ug by injection. By 21 days after the first dose antibodies of 1:40 were observed in 114 of the 120 subjects who received 15 ug and 106 out of 119 subjects who received the 30 ug. No deaths or adverse side effects were reported in either group. Local discomfort was reported by 56.3% of subjects and 53.8% reported systemic symptoms such as headaches. Nearly all were mild to moderate. ", "AssignmentId": "32RIADZISTPMTP9T3YWL9YNP2CM4SQ", "Question": "NEJMoa0907413", "WorkerId": "A2YUCJ28XANFOX", "Qualification": 0.625, "Topic": "immunization", "Hop": 1, "Education": "High School", "Gender": "female", "Age": "24-39", "level": 2, "branch": "NEJMoa0907413", "Tagging": {"Coarse": {"240": ["Participants"], "21": ["Intervention"], "local discomfort": ["Outcomes"], "systemic symptom": ["Outcomes"]}, "Fine": {"240": ["Sample-size"], "21": ["Duration"], "local discomfort": ["Adverse-effects"], "systemic symptom": ["Adverse-effects"]}}, "Doggos_crowd": {"Coarse": {"Participants": ["B", "C", "C", "A"], "Intervention": ["C", "A", "A"], "Outcomes": ["B", "A", "A"], "Conclusion": ["B"]}, "Fine": {"Age": ["B"], "Condition": ["C"], "Location": ["C"], "Sample-size": ["A"], "Intervention-general": ["C"], "Duration": ["A"], "Intensity": ["A"], "Outcomes-general": ["B"], "Effect-strength": ["A"], "Adverse-effects": ["A"], "Conclusion-general": ["B"]}}, "id": "NEJMoa0907413_32RIADZISTPMTP9T3YWL9YNP2CM4SQ", "children": [{"Answer": "we evaluated the immunogenicity and safety of the vaccine after each of two scheduled doses ,A single 15-ug dose and in 106 of 119 subjects (89.1 %) of 2009 H1N1 vaccine was immunogenic in adults , with mild to moderate vaccine associated reactions", "AssignmentId": "3K772S5NP9WFVIS6HAWZE6SE74NHE5", "Question": "NEJMoa0907413", "WorkerId": "A3F6TS7I3CSUM8", "Qualification": 0.625, "Topic": "immunization", "Hop": 2, "Education": "College", "Gender": "male", "Age": "24-39", "level": 3, "branch": "NEJMoa0907413", "Tagging": {"Coarse": {"immunogenicity": ["Outcomes"], "adult": ["Participants"], "106 of 119": ["Outcomes"], "89.1 %": ["Outcomes"], "2009 h1n1 vaccine": ["Intervention"]}, "Fine": {"immunogenicity": ["Outcomes-general"], "adult": ["Age"], "106 of 119": ["Effect-strength"], "89.1 %": ["Effect-strength"], "2009 h1n1 vaccine": ["Intervention-general"]}}, "Doggos_crowd": {"Coarse": {"Participants": ["B", "C", "C", "C"], "Intervention": ["A", "C", "B"], "Outcomes": ["A", "B", "C"], "Conclusion": ["A"]}, "Fine": {"Age": ["B"], "Condition": ["C"], "Location": ["C"], "Sample-size": ["C"], "Intervention-general": ["A"], "Duration": ["C"], "Intensity": ["B"], "Outcomes-general": ["A"], "Effect-strength": ["B"], "Adverse-effects": ["C"], "Conclusion-general": ["A"]}}, "id": "NEJMoa0907413_3K772S5NP9WFVIS6HAWZE6SE74NHE5", "children": [{"Answer": "A new flu virus has caused the first pandemic in 41 years. A study was done to find a safe and effective vaccine. The H1N1 vaccine is it.", "AssignmentId": "333U7HK6IA06UI9W9FO0K1Q8KL0JDV", "Question": "NEJMoa0907413", "WorkerId": "AAB13RUHSABEV", "Qualification": 0.875, "Topic": "immunization", "Hop": 3, "Education": "College", "Gender": "female", "Age": "40-60", "level": 4, "branch": "NEJMoa0907413", "Tagging": {"Coarse": {}, "Fine": {}}, "Doggos_crowd": {"Coarse": {"Participants": ["C", "C", "C", "C"], "Intervention": ["B", "C", "C"], "Outcomes": ["B", "C", "C"], "Conclusion": ["B"]}, "Fine": {"Age": ["C"], "Condition": ["C"], "Location": ["C"], "Sample-size": ["C"], "Intervention-general": ["B"], "Duration": ["C"], "Intensity": ["C"], "Outcomes-general": ["B"], "Effect-strength": ["C"], "Adverse-effects": ["C"], "Conclusion-general": ["B"]}}, "id": "NEJMoa0907413_333U7HK6IA06UI9W9FO0K1Q8KL0JDV", "children": [{"Answer": "Tests of a 2009 H1N1 vaccine proved successful with mild side effects.", "AssignmentId": "39JEC7537VM5GL3CQ8783JJKUBGVCJ", "Question": "NEJMoa0907413", "WorkerId": "AUPHYAKC58LPA", "Qualification": 0.625, "Topic": "immunization", "Hop": 4, "Education": "Some College", "Gender": "female", "Age": "24-39", "level": 5, "branch": "NEJMoa0907413", "Tagging": {"Coarse": {"2009 h1n1 vaccine": ["Intervention"]}, "Fine": {"2009 h1n1 vaccine": ["Intervention-general"]}}, "Doggos_crowd": {"Coarse": {"Participants": ["C", "C", "C", "C"], "Intervention": ["A", "C", "C"], "Outcomes": ["B", "C", "B"], "Conclusion": ["B"]}, "Fine": {"Age": ["C"], "Condition": ["C"], "Location": ["C"], "Sample-size": ["C"], "Intervention-general": ["A"], "Duration": ["C"], "Intensity": ["C"], "Outcomes-general": ["B"], "Effect-strength": ["C"], "Adverse-effects": ["B"], "Conclusion-general": ["B"]}}, "id": "NEJMoa0907413_39JEC7537VM5GL3CQ8783JJKUBGVCJ"}]}]}]}]}, {"Answer": "There was a widespread influenza A epidemic in 2009.  Researchers had to come up with a vaccine for influenza A.  More than 200 healthy adults between 18 and 64 years of age were recruited to be a part of a group study.  They were split into two groups and one group received 15 micrograms of hemagglutinin antigen while the other group received 30 micrograms.  After 21 days researchers measured antibodies and hemagglutination-inhibition in the members of the focus groups.   In the group that received the 15 microgram dosage antibodies were measured at 95.0% while the group that received 30 micrograms was at 89.1%.  Researchers repeated the same test and received almost the same results.  No serious reactions were reported among the memebers of the focus group.   An estimated 56% of the group members reported pain at the injection site after receiving the immunization.  Another 53% reported having headaches after receiving the injection.  The results of the study concluded that adults who received the 15 microgram dosage were immune to influenza A.", "AssignmentId": "3YT88D1N09J3NADHYBI087497E63K8", "Question": "NEJMoa0907413", "WorkerId": "A2XS5QI4YX493N", "Qualification": 0.75, "Topic": "immunization", "Hop": 0, "Education": "College", "Gender": "female", "Age": "24-39", "level": 1, "branch": "NEJMoa0907413", "Tagging": {"Coarse": {"healthy": ["Participants"], "adult": ["Participants"], "18 and 64": ["Participants"], "21": ["Intervention"], "95.0 %": ["Outcomes"], "89.1 %": ["Outcomes"]}, "Fine": {"healthy": ["Condition"], "adult": ["Age"], "18 and 64": ["Age"], "21": ["Duration"], "95.0 %": ["Effect-strength"], "89.1 %": ["Effect-strength"]}}, "Doggos_crowd": {"Coarse": {"Participants": ["A", "A", "C", "A"], "Intervention": ["B", "A", "A"], "Outcomes": ["A", "A", "A"], "Conclusion": ["A"]}, "Fine": {"Age": ["A"], "Condition": ["A"], "Location": ["C"], "Sample-size": ["A"], "Intervention-general": ["B"], "Duration": ["A"], "Intensity": ["A"], "Outcomes-general": ["A"], "Effect-strength": ["A"], "Adverse-effects": ["A"], "Conclusion-general": ["A"]}}, "id": "NEJMoa0907413_3YT88D1N09J3NADHYBI087497E63K8", "children": [{"Answer": "A simple flu virus is responsible for the first influenza pandemic in 41 years. Safe and effective vaccines are always needed and are currently being developed in Australia. This study is being conducted in healthy adults between the ages of 16-64. Controls were taken at the onset of study and administered 21 days apart and in random order and amounts. This study proved that a single 15-ug dose of the 2009 H1N1 vaccine was immunogenic in adults studied. &#13;", "AssignmentId": "3YGXWBAF7126M8KX6C6LUTJ7GANC4T", "Question": "NEJMoa0907413", "WorkerId": "A1AZV2XOQK7RSW", "Qualification": 0.875, "Topic": "immunization", "Hop": 1, "Education": "College", "Gender": "female", "Age": "40-60", "level": 2, "branch": "NEJMoa0907413", "Tagging": {"Coarse": {"healthy": ["Participants"], "adult": ["Participants"], "21": ["Intervention"], "australia": ["Participants"], "2009 h1n1 vaccine": ["Intervention"]}, "Fine": {"healthy": ["Condition"], "adult": ["Age"], "21": ["Duration"], "australia": ["Location"], "2009 h1n1 vaccine": ["Intervention-general"]}}, "Doggos_crowd": {"Coarse": {"Participants": ["B", "A", "B", "C"], "Intervention": ["A", "A", "B"], "Outcomes": ["A", "C", "C"], "Conclusion": ["B"]}, "Fine": {"Age": ["B"], "Condition": ["A"], "Location": ["B"], "Sample-size": ["C"], "Intervention-general": ["A"], "Duration": ["A"], "Intensity": ["B"], "Outcomes-general": ["A"], "Effect-strength": ["C"], "Adverse-effects": ["C"], "Conclusion-general": ["B"]}}, "id": "NEJMoa0907413_3YGXWBAF7126M8KX6C6LUTJ7GANC4T", "children": [{"Answer": "After the 2009 Influenza (H1N1) virus caused the first flu pandemic in 41 years, a small but rigorous study indicated that two small doses of an inactivated, split-virus 2009 H1N1 vaccine administered 21 days apart was both safe and effective in healthy adults.", "AssignmentId": "3Z9WI9EOZ09IHIKGDW72C15JR1KKHT", "Question": "NEJMoa0907413", "WorkerId": "A1H4RXFUNZGXIT", "Qualification": 0.75, "Topic": "immunization", "Hop": 2, "Education": "Some College", "Gender": "female", "Age": "40-60", "level": 3, "branch": "NEJMoa0907413", "Tagging": {"Coarse": {"healthy": ["Participants"], "adult": ["Participants"], "21": ["Intervention"], "2009 h1n1 vaccine": ["Intervention"]}, "Fine": {"healthy": ["Condition"], "adult": ["Age"], "21": ["Duration"], "2009 h1n1 vaccine": ["Intervention-general"]}}, "Doggos_crowd": {"Coarse": {"Participants": ["B", "A", "C", "C"], "Intervention": ["A", "A", "B"], "Outcomes": ["C", "C", "C"], "Conclusion": ["C"]}, "Fine": {"Age": ["B"], "Condition": ["A"], "Location": ["C"], "Sample-size": ["C"], "Intervention-general": ["A"], "Duration": ["A"], "Intensity": ["B"], "Outcomes-general": ["C"], "Effect-strength": ["C"], "Adverse-effects": ["C"], "Conclusion-general": ["C"]}}, "id": "NEJMoa0907413_3Z9WI9EOZ09IHIKGDW72C15JR1KKHT", "children": [{"Answer": "It was found that a single 15ug dose of 2009 H1N1 vaccine was immunogenic in adults aged 18 to 64 years, with mild to moderate reactions.", "AssignmentId": "3JAOYWH7VJP0MIKF0KVBEKKAXPS9L8", "Question": "NEJMoa0907413", "WorkerId": "AON59V5VZU2AK", "Qualification": 0.5, "Topic": "immunization", "Hop": 3, "Education": "College", "Gender": "female", "Age": "40-60", "level": 4, "branch": "NEJMoa0907413", "Tagging": {"Coarse": {"adult": ["Participants"], "2009 h1n1 vaccine": ["Intervention"]}, "Fine": {"adult": ["Age"], "2009 h1n1 vaccine": ["Intervention-general"]}}, "Doggos_crowd": {"Coarse": {"Participants": ["A", "C", "C", "C"], "Intervention": ["A", "C", "B"], "Outcomes": ["A", "B", "C"], "Conclusion": ["A"]}, "Fine": {"Age": ["A"], "Condition": ["C"], "Location": ["C"], "Sample-size": ["C"], "Intervention-general": ["A"], "Duration": ["C"], "Intensity": ["B"], "Outcomes-general": ["A"], "Effect-strength": ["C"], "Adverse-effects": ["B"], "Conclusion-general": ["A"]}}, "id": "NEJMoa0907413_3JAOYWH7VJP0MIKF0KVBEKKAXPS9L8", "children": [{"Answer": "Single H1N1 dose (15-ug) was immunogenic in adults.", "AssignmentId": "3AZHRG4CU551AK6DUI8IPNP0U2Y309", "Question": "NEJMoa0907413", "WorkerId": "A2YTQDLACTLIBA", "Qualification": 0.875, "Topic": "immunization", "Hop": 4, "Education": "College", "Gender": "female", "Age": "60+", "level": 5, "branch": "NEJMoa0907413", "Tagging": {"Coarse": {"adult": ["Participants"]}, "Fine": {"adult": ["Age"]}}, "Doggos_crowd": {"Coarse": {"Participants": ["B", "C", "C", "C"], "Intervention": ["B", "B", "C"], "Outcomes": ["A", "C", "C"], "Conclusion": ["B"]}, "Fine": {"Age": ["B"], "Condition": ["C"], "Location": ["C"], "Sample-size": ["C"], "Intervention-general": ["B"], "Duration": ["C"], "Intensity": ["B"], "Outcomes-general": ["A"], "Effect-strength": ["C"], "Adverse-effects": ["C"], "Conclusion-general": ["B"]}}, "id": "NEJMoa0907413_3AZHRG4CU551AK6DUI8IPNP0U2Y309"}]}]}]}]}]}